3etown.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy notice - Etown Electronics

The following Privacy Policy applies only to 3etown.com and information of our customers collected online through 3etown.com. Your privacy is very important to us and definitely confidencial.   
3etown respects and protects the privacy of its visitors. In this document, we explain how we use the information you supply us. If we update our Privacy Policy, all revisions will be posted on this page. We reserve the right to change the privacy policy any time.   
Personally identifiable information may include information that you provide us by requesting information when registering for special offers or programs or when you purchase products online. This may include your name, address (including billing and shipping addresses), telephone number, e-mail address, organization, city, state and zip code. We may use this information to process and ship orders to contact you about the status of your order, and to contact you with answers to your questions, or to provide information about new and exciting products, services, promotions and corporate-related information. We may use mailings, telephone calls and e-mails to contact you.   
You also may create an account through 3etown.com at any time by providing your email address and creating a unique password. An account is not required to visit our site or to place an order at MicroEtown.com. Creating an account allows you to save order information, order history, track status of your orders and set your ordering preferences. For your privacy and security, we do not store credit card or Gift Card numbers in your account. You may change saved account information anytime. Simply visit the Your Account page, log in with your email address and password.

Removal or Edit of Your Information  
If you have registered for Special E-mail Offerings, you may unsubscribe from the program, by visiting the e-mail unsubscribe page or click on the links available at the bottom of any of these special offer e-mails. You may also request the removal of your information by contacting us via e-mail.   
If you wish to receive more personalized information from 3etown or change anything about your profile such as your e-mail format, please click on the links available at the bottom of any of these special offer e-mails or visit the Your Profile page.  
Non-personally identifiable information is collected without any direct association with you specifically. In the normal course of using 3etown.com, we may collect information about your habits and usage of our sites.

An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are using Internet. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. 3etown collects IP addresses for the system administrational purposes, to report aggregated information and audit the use of our site. If we are required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena, we will provide these IP addresses to the proper authorities.   
Sharing and Disclosure Your Information

Agents, employees and contractors of 3etown who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and the high standards of the corporation.   
Information about you specifically will not be used for any other purpose and we will carry out the services you requested from 3etown.   
We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone at any time.   
We will not use any personal information beyond what is necessary to assist us in delivering to you the services you have requested.   
We may send personally identifiable information about you to other organizations when:   
We have your consent to share the information.   
We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested.   
We are required to do so by law.   
You may delete these files from your computer at any time. You can set your web browser to notify you if such information is about to be placed on your computer, and you can choose the option in your web browser to refuse it. If you refuse the information, you may not be able to make full use of the features on our web site.   
If you elect to use our "Email Your Wish List" service for informing a friend about our site or products you are interested in, we may ask for your email address, your name, the email address or the name of your friend and the email address of your friend. 3etown will automatically send the friend a one-time email on your behalf. 3etown does not store this information. It is only used for sending this one time email.

**Limited Liability**   
In no event shall we be liable for any indirect, special, incidental, consequential or punitive damages whether in an action in contract, tort, equity or otherwise, arising out of or in any way connected with the use of or inability to use this site or the materials therein or resulting from unauthorized access to or alteration of Date. The parties acknowledge that this is a reasonable allocation of risk.  
 ****

**Children**  
The site and its services are not directed to, and not intended for the use of children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any reviews of products or services or any personal information to the site or the Review Service.   
Changes to These Terms   
3etown reserves the right to change or modify any of the terms and conditions contained in these Site Terms, or any policy of the site, from time to time at any time and in its sole discretion. If Dino Direct decides to change these Site Terms or a Site policies, it will post a new version on the site and update the effective date set forth above. Any changes or modifications to these Site Terms will be effective upon posting of the revisions. Your continued use of the site following posting of any changes or modifications constitute your acceptance of such changes or modifications.We are committed to making your experience at 3etown.com enjoyful and rewarding.

**Restriction on Use**   
No permission is granted for use the materials, information, text or graphics, and/or to hyperlink other websites with this website, or to use the materials on your website in any way or for any reason without prior specific authorization from 3etown.com.

**Disclaimer**  
There are certain risks in using any information, software, or products found on internet; and MicroEtown cautions you to be certain that you completely understand these risks before retrieving, using, relying upon, or purchasing anything via internet.

Visitors to this website assume all responsibility and risk for the use of this website. Information published on this website is provided without charge as a convenience to visitors, to be used for informational purposes only. NOTHING IN THIS WEBSITE CONSTITUTES A RECOMMENDATION OR ENDORSEMENT OF ANY ITEM, PRODUCT OR BRAND.

**Limitation of Liability**   
3etown is not responsible for any infections, contaminations, delay in operation or transmission, line failure, errors, omissions, interruptions, or defects arising out of your use of this site or with respect to the material provided and/or contained on this site.

In no event shall 3etown be responsible for any special, direct, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages, or any other damages of any kind, resulting from whatever cause, including but not limited to loss of use, loss profits, or loss of data, whether in an action under theories of contract, negligence, strict liability, or otherwise, arising out of or in any way in connection with the use of or inability to use the information or materials on, or accessed through, the 3etown Web Site.
